// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Which of the following protects the body against infectious disease and foreign invaders?",
    answer: "Leukocytes",
    options: [
      "Red blood cells",
      "Endoplasmic reticulum",
      "Leukocytes",
      "Golgi apparatus"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Maximum number of animals species belong to which among the following groups?",
    answer: "Arthropoda",
    options: [
      "Arthropoda",
      "Pisces",
      "Aves",
      "Mammalia"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "In which among the following organ, “Bowman’s Capsule” is found?",
    answer: "Kidney",
    options: [
      "Liver",
      "Kidney",
      "Heart",
      "Small intestine"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Who is the father of Botany?",
    answer: "Theophrastus",
    options: [
      "Adam Smith",
      "Greco-Roman",
      "Theophrastus",
      "Carl Linnaeur"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Ohm is a unit of measuring _________?",
    answer: "Resistance",
    options: [
      "Resistance",
      "Current",
      "Voltage",
      "None of the above"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 6,
    question: "If we look at the floating piece of iceberg on the sea, approximately what fraction of it is visible above the seawater level?",
    answer: "1/8th",
    options: [
      "1/6th",
      "1/8th",
      "1/10th",
      "1/5th"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 7,
    question: "White Phosphorous is represented by which among the following symbols?",
    answer: "P4",
    options: [
      "P1",
      "P2",
      "P3",
      "P4"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 8,
    question: "Identify the thermosetting plastic from the given options:",
    answer: "Bakelite",
    options: [
      "Polythene",
      "Bakelite",
      "Polyvincychloride",
      "Casseine"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Which compound of mercury is used as antiseptic?",
    answer: "Mercuric chloride",
    options: [
      "Mercuric sulphide",
      "Mercuric oxide",
      "Mercuric chloride",
      "None of the above"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 10,
    question: "Which among the following is a common salt in Detergents?",
    answer: "Sulphate",
    options: [
      "Sulphate",
      "Nitrate",
      "Sulphonate",
      "Carbonate"
    ]
  },
  // you can uncomment the below codes and make duplicate as more as you want to add question
  // but remember you need to give the numb value serialize like 1,2,3,5,6,7,8,9.....

  //   {
  //   numb: 6,
  //   question: "Your Question is Here",
  //   answer: "Correct answer of the question is here",
  //   options: [
  //     "Option 1",
  //     "option 2",
  //     "option 3",
  //     "option 4"
  //   ]
  // },
];